xmlsitemapgenerator.org 2019-05-01

# Xml Sitemap Generator • End User Licence Agreement (EULA)

## Privacy policy

When you use our service you are indicating your agreement to the privacy policy. 

Our service is automated and unsupported. If you choose to use the service you agree to the End Use Licence Agreement (EULA) and this privacy policy.

### How we use your data

We use information about you in the following ways: 

  * Help fullfil your request when using our online service.
  * Notify you as your request passes through our system.
  * Enable us to review and improve our website, applications and services.
  * Provide customer support where applicable.
  * Carry out analysis or where we seek your thoughts and opinions on the services we provide.
  * Notify you about changes to our website, terms & conditions, services or prices.

Where posible we will anonymise or pseudonymise you data so that it can no longer be associated with you (such as for statistial analysis), in which case we may use it without further notice to you. 

If you contact us we may also hold personal data about you although in general we do not provide support for direct contact other than through public social media channels. 

### Access to your personal data

Communication as part of using the service are automated.

Any further access you you personal data is limited to people who need access in order for us to fulfil the purpose, such as support requests.

We do not sell or pass on your details to 3rd parties for marketting or sales puposes.

As the service develops we may transfer ownership of the service to a trusted 3rd party. At this time it may be necessary to pass details to the 3rd party to enable them to carry on running the service.

We primerily use Microsoft Azure for hosting the service. We will use database resources located in the EU regions as defined by Microsoft.

Web server locations can vary depending on where you are using the service from and your website loation.

### Retention of your data

When you use this service we temporarily store your data whilst we fullfil your request. After a period (usually less than 14 days) this will automatically be erased.

For statistical purposes we may keep a record of the types of features and requests being made to help us better understand how the service is being used.

### Website Cookies

Cookies are small files placed on your computer which enable websites to store bits of information.

We do not use cookies to store personal information.

In order to bring you this service we use cookies to:

  * Maintain your user session and login.
  * Track basic usage statistics for our website, using third parties such as google.
  * Display adverts using third parties such as google.
  * Interact with third party services such as facebook and YouTube.

Our cookies are anonymous and do not include personal details.

Whilst every effort is made to ensure we only deal with reputable services from the likes of Google, Facebook, YouTube, Twitter, PayPal, etc. we do not accept any liability for their actions.

By using this website you agree to accept these cookies. You may also block them through your web browser, however this may limit your ability to use our services.

### External website links

Within our website we provide links to external website for futher information. We do not endorse or control these websites they are simply supplied "as is" for further reading. We would recommend you review and terms of use and privacy statements of these websites.

### Website security

This is a small community website with limited resources, however we have taken reasonable measures in this context to prevent unauthorised acess to your data.

We use HTTPS / SSL to encypt traffic between you and our website

To minimise risk we have tried to limit the data we store as in the "Retention of your data" section

We use Microsoft Azure to provide reliable and secure hosting.

Where possible resources are secured using 2 factor authenticaiton to prevent unauthorised access.

We have tried to limit the need for indivduals to access your data by automating processes within our website.

### Your rights

Under data protection law you have various rights.

When you use this service we temporarily store your email address while we fullfil your request. After a period (usually less than 14 days) this will automatically be erased.
